bitinfocharts.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy policy

### Privacy policy

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)

**What information do we collect?**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on site. You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Disclaimer

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by bitinfocharts.com and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, bitinfocharts.com takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.

Any exchange rates displayed are provided by 3rd party services.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://bitinfocharts.com/  
bitinfocharts@gmail.com

Contact:    Donations: BTC 13KPgojUhg2Rx92WRJQDZR7vy2vegonHsf  /  DOGE D86cPCwS4CQEiXsTHU3r5fTXToujJsCmax    Privacy Policy / Disclaimer
